Fulton Lewis Jr. Papers
Fulton Lewis Jr. Papers
- Part I. Personal file
  - Lectures and trips
    - Grande Forks, North Dakota, 1965 (Box 139)
    - Brownwood, Texas, 1965 (Box 139)
    - Birmingham, Alabama, 1965 (Box 139)
    - Los Angeles, California, 1965 (Box 139)
    - Portland, Oregon, 1965 (Box 139)
    - Terre Haute, Indiana, 1966 (Box 139)
    - Canton, Ohio, 1966 (Box 139)
    - Miscellaneous, 1945; undated (Box 139)
    - Azusa, California, undated (Box 139)
  - Family items
    - Air Force Medal (Box 139)
    - Balance of Elizabeth's estate in the bank (Box 139)
    - Betsy Lewis (Box 140)
    - Fulton Lewis III and Betsy Lewis bulletins (Box 140)
    - Betsy Lewis high school book (Box 140)
    - Diary, passport, mementos (Box 140)
    - Fulton Lewis degrees (Box 141)
    - Fulton Lewis, Jr.
      - Fan letter file (Box 141)
      - Personal correspondence (Box 141)
      - Diploma (Box 141)
      - Medical report (Box 141)
      - Report about (Box 141)
      - School papers (Box 141)
      - Horoscope (Box 141)
      - Compositions, 1922-1923 (Box 141)
    - Placid Harbor plans (Box 141)
    - Letters (Box 141)
    - Literary works of Fulton Lewis, Jr. (Box 141)
    - Mrs. Lewis' horticultural awards (Box 141)
    - Most Interesting Experience (Box 141)
  - Scrapbooks
    - [Untitled] (Box 142)
    - [Untitled] (Box 143)
    - [Untitled] (Box 144)
    - [Untitled] (Box 145)
    - [Untitled] (Box 145A)
    - [Untitled] (Box 145B)
    - [Untitled] (Box 146)
    - Mrs. Lewis, Inaugural Committee, 1953 (Box 147)
    - Placid Harbor furnishings (Box 147)
    - Publicity, Fulton Lewis, Jr. (Box 147)
    - Real estate, blue prints (Box 147)
    - Music by Fulton Lewis, Jr. (Box 147)
  - Awards
    - #17 Washington Times-Herald (Box 148)
    - #13 Sigma Delta Chi (Box 148)
    - #12 Rockford Chamber of Commerce (Box 148)
    - #11 National Association of frozen food manufacturers (Box 148)
    - #9 Houston Junior Chamber of Commerce (Box 148)
    - #8 Horizon Land Corp.-Arizona (Box 148)
    - #7 Knights of Columbus-Dover, New Hampshire (Box 148)
    - #5 Anti-Communist Confederation of Polish freedom fighters (Box 148)
    - #6 Chicago Better Business Bureau, Inc. (Box 148)
    - #3 American Legion (Box 148)
    - #4 American Legion (Box 148)
    - Sales Executives Club of N.Y. (Box 149)
    - McKinley, Gaven (Box 149)
    - Awards correspondence (Box 149)
    - Miscellaneous awards A-D (Box 149)
    - DuPont Radio Commentator Award (Box 149)
    - Miscellaneous awards E-Y (Box 149)
    - Fight Communism Committee Award of Merit (Box 149)
    - Senate of Texas Award (Box 149)
  - Photos
    - Fulton Lewis, Jr.
      - Self portraits (Box 150)
      - On podium (Box 150)
      - Behind podium (Box 150)
      - Speaking (Box 150)
      - Front of the capitol (Box 150)
      - Office work (Box 150)
      - Engagement (Box 150)
      - Receiving awards (Box 150)
      - Advertising (Box 151)
      - On the farm (Box 151)
      - Family (Box 151)
      - Church choir (Box 151)
      - Canton Baptist Temple (Box 151)
      - Garage scenes (Box 151)
      - Military scenes (Box 151)
      - Negatives (Box 151)
      - Travel (Box 151)
      - Fulton Lewis III (Box 151)
      - Claudius Huston (Box 151)
      - Misc. (Box 151)
    - Autographed photos of others
      - Joseph Stalin (Box 151)
      - Chiang Kai-Shek (Box 151)
      - James A. Farley (Box 151)
      - Clifford Barryman (Box 151)
  - #1 The National Society of Children of the Am. Rev. and Alfred J. DuPont Radio Awards foundation (Box 151A)
  - American Jewish League Against Communism (Box 151B)
  - #16-United Business Men's Association of Phila. (Box 151C)
  - Mutual Broadcasting Syst. - in memory of F.L. (Box 151D)
  - F.L. Photographic Records (Box 151E)
  - Drawings
    - Andrual, Marietta Minningirode (Box 152)
    - Baer, "Quick Takes" (Box 152)
    - Berryman, C.K., Dec 1935, 1937, Feb 1939 (Box 152)
    - "Chairman Huston" (Box 152)
    - Crosby, P., Aug 1937
    - Nicholson, R.W., "U.S. Atomic Secrets" (Box 152)
    - Parish, Joe, "The Boss Chair", 1954 (Box 152)
  - Award #18 (Box 152A)
- Part I. Audiovisual material
  Access to recordings requires advance notice to produce a listening copy.
  - Audiotapes
    - Barnes & Kimel Furn Co, Mr. Stanley Weam, lewis_f_jr_0245; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Barry Goldwater, 06/15/1964; lewis_f_jr_0188; more information inside of recording box; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - Betsy, lewis_f_jr_0309; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - Bill Scholtz, lewis_f_jr_0295; label is partially damaged.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - Bill Scholtz, lewis_f_jr_0296; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - Bill Shultz, Tape 3, lewis_f_jr_0302; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - Bill Shultz, Tape 5, lewis_f_jr_0314; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 162)
    - Bill Shultz, Tape 8, lewis_f_jr_0303; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - Bookmailer Spots, lewis_f_jr_0247; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Buddy & mouth organ "Ruby", lewis_f_jr_0207; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Buddy [unused?], lewis_f_jr_0246; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Chinese Christmas, lewis_f_jr_0199; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Christmas, lewis_f_jr_0300; sticker on the reel reads: Blank; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - Church, 02/14/1954; lewis_f_jr_0268; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - Church at Lewis Home, 02/21/1954; lewis_f_jr_0256; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Church Service Recording From Lewis Rome, 03/28/1954; lewis_f_jr_0206; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Church Service taken at home Lewis, 07/12/1953; lewis_f_jr_0236; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - Church Service taken at home Lewis, lewis_f_jr_0237; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - Church Service - recorded from Mr. Lewis home #1 of 8, 04/03/1954; lewis_f_jr_0248; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - [Church service?] #2 of 8, lewis_f_jr_0253; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Church Service #3 of 8, 03/07/1954; lewis_f_jr_0255; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - [Church service?] #4 of 8, lewis_f_jr_0251; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Coffee Club and Joni James "Dansero"; "Intro for Coffee Club and Jimmy Rogers"; Uh Oh I’m Falling in Love Again"; Agilon Outs, lewis_f_jr_0270; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - Commentaries; Dorothy Healy on KPFK, 03/03/1961; 03/17/1961; 04/02/1961; lewis_f_jr_0294; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - Cuba - Broadcast of Fulton Lewis Jr. Tape #1, lewis_f_jr_0205; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Cuba - Broadcast of Fulton Lewis Jr. Tape #2, lewis_f_jr_0200; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Duplicate Copy of Reel 2B; #1 of 5 Reels, lewis_f_jr_0233; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - Dr. Rusden - Baron Lywinsky Kirchner, 11/14/1954; lewis_f_jr_0252; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Easter Sunday Hollywood M. Church, 04/18/1954; lewis_f_jr_0194; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - F. Lewis Jr. Special Spots, 11/09/1957; lewis_f_jr_0254; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Fulton Lewis, 01/26/1953; lewis_f_jr_0195; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Fulton Lewis, lewis_f_jr_0293; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - Fulton Lewis Broadcast, lewis_f_jr_0191; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - Fulton Lewis Guatamala #2, lewis_f_jr_0182; 1/4 inch audio tape, running time 00:08:00 (Box 153)
    - Fulton Lewis Jr; Northwest Airline Counter Nat’l Airport - Washington D.C., 12/15/1954; 12/16/1954; lewis_f_jr_0284; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - Fulton Lewis Jr Aircopy, 08/12/1959; lewis_f_jr_0196; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Fulton Lewis Jr Book Mailer "Bending the Twig", 11/23/1951; 11/23/1951; lewis_f_jr_0203; produced by KTHT; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Fulton Lewis Jr Broadcast, 11/22/1951; 11/23/1951; lewis_f_jr_0202; produced by KTHT; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Fulton Lewis Jr from Tokyo, lewis_f_jr_0283; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - Fulton Lewis Jr Openings, 06/15/1964; lewis_f_jr_0190; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - Fulton Lewis Jr Openings, 09/14/1956; lewis_f_jr_0198; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Fulton Lewis Jr. Broadcast Abord the SS United States Interview with Mr. Epsy, lewis_f_jr_0192; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - Fulton Lewis Opening Done Twice, lewis_f_jr_0287; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - Fulton Lewis Protection, lewis_f_jr_0250; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Fulton Lewis show; Chinese Plane, 08/22/1966; lewis_f_jr_0215; produced by Robert F. Hurleigh; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 155)
    - Fulton Lewis Spots, 06/21/1951; lewis_f_jr_0286; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - Fulton Lewis, Jr. in Spartanburg, S.C. Side 1 - Address; Side 2 - Interview with Mr. Lewis conducted by Jack Buttram of WMUU, AM-FM Greenville, S.C., the voice of Bob Jones University -- the World’s Most Unusual University, lewis_f_jr_0291; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - Fulton Lewis, N. G., lewis_f_jr_0304; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - Goldwater - Lewis statement; 1) statement; 2) Q & A; 3) Q & A, 06/15/1964; lewis_f_jr_0189; more information inside of recording box.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - Hon. W. Lee O’Daniel 5 minute Speech, lewis_f_jr_0181; speech made by Hon. W. Lee O’Daniel; more information included in recording’s box.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - Hospital Ball, 05/16/1953; lewis_f_jr_0184; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - If I Loved You, lewis_f_jr_0285; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - In the Beginning, lewis_f_jr_0258; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - Interview with Robert Hutchins, lewis_f_jr_0211; produced by Tex2Jinx WRCA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 155)
    - KCUB Radio DeRoy Jewelers - DeRoy Spots - 4 Spots, lewis_f_jr_0290; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - Know Your Constitutional Government, 12/1957; 01/21/1958; lewis_f_jr_0216; 1/4 inch audio tape, running time 00:00:58 (Box 155)
    - Memphis. Dean Manion Interview; Fulton Lewis Jr, 09/14/1956; lewis_f_jr_0197; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Mr. C.M. Beyer -Tape #1 AFT Session, 01/25/1961; 08/16/1961; lewis_f_jr_0193; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - N. G. ? Church, lewis_f_jr_0312; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 162)
    - N. G. Army - McCarthy, lewis_f_jr_0298; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - N. G. Church, lewis_f_jr_0299; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - N. G. Church, lewis_f_jr_0306; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - N. G. Church, lewis_f_jr_0311; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 162)
    - Opening Transcriptions for Fulton LEwis Jr. Show, 09/12/1951; lewis_f_jr_0277; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - PTA Institute Albany Hotel, 11/09/1961; lewis_f_jr_0209; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 155)
    - Reel #1 of 5 reels of #2a, lewis_f_jr_0242; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - Reel #1 of 5 reels of #2a, lewis_f_jr_0243; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - Reel #3 of 5 Reels; Duplicate Copy of Reel #1B, 02/14/1954; lewis_f_jr_0267; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - Reel #3 of 5 Reels; duplicate Copy of Reel 2B, lewis_f_jr_0261; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - Reel #3 of 5 reels Duplicate Copy of Reel #2A, lewis_f_jr_0244; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Reel #4 of 5 Reels; Duplicate Copy of Reel #2A, lewis_f_jr_0265; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - Reel #4 of 5 Reels; Duplicate Copy of Reel #2A, lewis_f_jr_0266; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - Reel #4 of 5 Reels, Duplicate Copy of Reel 1B, lewis_f_jr_0241; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - Reel #4 of 5 Reels, Duplicate Copy of Reel 2B, lewis_f_jr_0238; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - Reel #5 of 5 Reels Duplicate Copy of Reel #1B, lewis_f_jr_0263; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - Reel #5 of 5 Reels, Duplicate Copy of Reel 2B, lewis_f_jr_0239; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - Reel #5 of 5 Reels, Duplicate Copy of Reel 2B, 10/04/1953; lewis_f_jr_0240; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - Reel #5 of 5 ReelsDuplicate Copy of Reel #2A, lewis_f_jr_0262; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - Report Note Kovacs Story (Donald Saltz interview) cut interview for broadcast, 01/24/1961; lewis_f_jr_0217; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 155)
    - Reporters’ Roundup Transcript, 03/03/1958; lewis_f_jr_0208; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - Retma, 01/26/1959; lewis_f_jr_0289; produced by John B Lewis; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - Rev. Robert Moon of Fresno, CA at State College San Diego, CA, 03/14/1961; lewis_f_jr_0276; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - Sponsored by League of Women Voters, lewis_f_jr_0259; produced by KQED; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - Staples, lewis_f_jr_0307; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - Tape #1, 12/15/1954; lewis_f_jr_0232; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - Tape 6, lewis_f_jr_0308; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - Tape 7, lewis_f_jr_0313; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 162)
    - Tape 9, lewis_f_jr_0315; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 162)
    - Tape of TV Program Chiang, lewis_f_jr_0212; produced by Tex2Jinx WRCA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 155)
    - Tex & Jinx McRary Interview with Robert Hutchins, lewis_f_jr_0213; produced by Tex2Jinx WRCA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 155)
    - Transcripts of Broadcast by Joseph L. Rauh Jr, 06/25/1956; lewis_f_jr_0210; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 155)
    - Tribute to Fulton Lewis Jr., 08/22/1966; lewis_f_jr_0186; more information inside of recording box.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - Tribute to Fulton Lewis Jr., 08/22/1966; lewis_f_jr_0187; more information inside of recording box.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - Trio Hollywood Choir, lewis_f_jr_0257; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - Two lectures on Communism by Dr. John R. Lechner, Executive Director of Americanism Educational League of Los Angeles about Operation Abolition, 09/05/1961; lewis_f_jr_0274; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - UNESCO #3, lewis_f_jr_0292; produced by Dr. William Lawlor; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - Unesco Debate Side 1 and 2, lewis_f_jr_0183; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - We The People - Declaration of Independence, 1957; lewis_f_jr_0201; produced by A Better World to Live In; more information inside of recording box; 1/4 inch audio tape, running time 02:00:00 (Box 154)
    - Whitney Bolton Commentary, 08/22/1966; lewis_f_jr_0185; more information inside of recording box.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 153)
    - The World Today; Fulton Lewis, Jr. Special Memorial, 08/22/1966; lewis_f_jr_0214; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 155)
    - Xmas Work Print, 12/22/1958; lewis_f_jr_0204; produced by St. David’s Episcopal; more information inside of the recording box.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 154)
    - [untitled fragments], lewis_f_jr_0281; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0234; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0235; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 156)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0249; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 157)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0260; 1/4 inch audio tape, running time 01:11:00 (Box 158)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0264; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - [untitled], 02/14/1954; lewis_f_jr_0269; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0271; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 158)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0272; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0273; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0275; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0278; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0279; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0280; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0282; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 159)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0288; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0297; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 160)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0301; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0305; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 161)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0310; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 162)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0316; miscellaneous notes are written inside the tape box. A business card of George E. Ross is inserted into the box.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 162)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0317; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 163)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0318; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 163)
    - [untitled], lewis_f_jr_0319; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 163)
  - Films
    Films are individually barcoded. Please request by title and ID number (e.g., lewis_f_jr_0442).
    - #29, lewis_f_jr_0442; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - #29 (2), lewis_f_jr_0443; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - A.D.A.; H Dexter White; Communist Counterfeiting, lewis_f_jr_0428; Film: 16mm, color, monaural
    - ADA, 06/22/1954; lewis_f_jr_0001; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - ADA, lewis_f_jr_0458; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Air Force Academy, lewis_f_jr_0441; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Air Force Academy, lewis_f_jr_0450; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Air Force Academy, lewis_f_jr_0474; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Air Force Academy (1), 05/24/1955; lewis_f_jr_0003; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Air Force Academy (2), lewis_f_jr_0004; Film: 16mm
    - Air Force Academy (3), lewis_f_jr_0005; Film: 16mm
    - Airlift to Berlin, lewis_f_jr_0002; produced by Flory Films, Inc.; Film: 16mm, color
    - Alaska, lewis_f_jr_0006; Film: 16mm
    - Alaska (1) 1954, lewis_f_jr_0007; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Alaska, McCarthy, lewis_f_jr_0008; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - American Red Cross Report - Fulton Lewis Jr Pilot Film, 1954; lewis_f_jr_0226; produced by United Television Programs; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Argonne Atomic Lab, lewis_f_jr_0426; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Atomic Energy, lewis_f_jr_0439; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Atomic Energy (10) [Argonne Labs], 1954; lewis_f_jr_0483; produced by WALA-TV; General Teleradio Film Division; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Atomic Energy (Argonne Labs) (1), lewis_f_jr_0009; Film: 16mm
    - Atomic Energy (Argonne Labs) (2), 03/28/1955; lewis_f_jr_0010; Film: 16mm
    - Atomic Energy (Argonne Labs) (3), lewis_f_jr_0011; Film: 16mm
    - Atomic Energy (Argonne Labs) (4), lewis_f_jr_0012; Film: 16mm
    - Atomic Energy (Argonne Labs) (5), 06/01/1955; lewis_f_jr_0013; Film: 16mm
    - Atomic Energy (Argonne Labs) (6), 04/18/1955; lewis_f_jr_0014; Film: 16mm
    - Atomic Energy (Argonne Labs) (7), lewis_f_jr_0015; Film: 16mm
    - Atomic Energy (Argonne Labs) (8), lewis_f_jr_0016; Film: 16mm
    - Bootcie [?], 1947; lewis_f_jr_0503; Copy of handwritten note on the old can is inserted with the film. It reads: “N148 N [illegible] - Fine Grain, NY, For R2”.; Film: 16mm
    - Brainwashing (Part 1), 04/07/1954; lewis_f_jr_0017; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Brainwashing No. 2, 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0018; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Central America, 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0518; Synopsis of the Fulton Lewis Jr. TV Show No. 21 is accompanying the film.; Film: 16mm; running time 11:33
    - Chang Kai Shek [sic], lewis_f_jr_0470; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Chenault [sic], lewis_f_jr_0423; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Chenault [sic], lewis_f_jr_0448; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Chenault [sic], lewis_f_jr_0509; Note on the leader reads: “F. Lewis Jr. No. 13; A”. Interview with Major General Claire Chennault.; Film: 16mm
    - Chennault (1), lewis_f_jr_0019; Film: 16mm
    - Chennault (2), lewis_f_jr_0020; Film: 16mm
    - Chennault (3), lewis_f_jr_0021; Film: 16mm
    - Chennault (4), lewis_f_jr_0022; Film: 16mm
    - Chiang-Kai-Shek, lewis_f_jr_0038; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Chiang-Kai-Shek (1), lewis_f_jr_0023; Film: 16mm
    - Chiang-Kai-Shek (2), lewis_f_jr_0024; Film: 16mm
    - Chiang-Kai-Shek (3), lewis_f_jr_0025; Film: 16mm
    - Chiang-Kai-Shek (4), lewis_f_jr_0026; Film: 16mm
    - Chiang-Kai-Shek (5), lewis_f_jr_0027; Film: 16mm
    - Chiang-Kai-Shek (6), lewis_f_jr_0028; Film: 16mm
    - Chiang-Kai-Shek (7), lewis_f_jr_0029; Film: 16mm
    - Churchill (1), lewis_f_jr_0030; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Churchill (2), lewis_f_jr_0031; Film: 16mm
    - Coffee Prices (1), 1954; lewis_f_jr_0032; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Coffee Prices (2), 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0033; Fulton Lewis, Jr. Television Show; Film: 16mm, b/w, running time 11:25
    - Communist China, 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0039; Fulton Lewis, Jr. Television Show, Episode 4; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Congressman McCormick [sic], lewis_f_jr_0517; Film: 16mm
    - Continental Air Defense Command, lewis_f_jr_0040; film may actually be "Picket Ship," as identified on the head and tail, rather than "Continental Air Defense Command," as it was identified on the original metal film can; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Economics, 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0034; Fulton Lewis, Jr. Television Show, Episode 23; Film: 16mm, b/w, running time 11:39
    - Economics, lewis_f_jr_0520; Note on the original leader reads: “Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 24”.; Film: 16mm
    - Elections, 1954; lewis_f_jr_0041; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Europe (1), lewis_f_jr_0035; Film: 8mm
    - Europe (2), lewis_f_jr_0036; Film: 8mm
    - Europe (3), lewis_f_jr_0037; Film: 8mm
    - F.B.I., lewis_f_jr_0091; Film: 16mm
    - F.B.I. (1), 07/16/1955; lewis_f_jr_0042; Film: 16mm
    - F.B.I. (2), lewis_f_jr_0043; Film: 16mm
    - F.B.I., No. 1, lewis_f_jr_0433; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - F.H.A., 1951; lewis_f_jr_0451; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - F.H.A., lewis_f_jr_0092; Film: 16mm
    - F.H.A. (1), lewis_f_jr_0045; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - F.H.A. (2), lewis_f_jr_0046; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - F.H.A. (3), lewis_f_jr_0047; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - F.H.A. (4), 01/09/1954; lewis_f_jr_0048; Fulton Lewis, Jr. Television Show, Episode 17; Film: 16mm, b/w, running time 11:59
    - FBI (2) (Show 16), lewis_f_jr_0461; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Fence Buster, Babe Ruth, lewis_f_jr_0044; Greatest Drama, Episode 1; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Formosa, lewis_f_jr_0449; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Formosa, lewis_f_jr_0455; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Formosa (1), lewis_f_jr_0049; Film: 16mm
    - Formosa (2), lewis_f_jr_0050; Film: 16mm
    - Formosa (3), lewis_f_jr_0051; Film: 16mm
    - Formosa (4), lewis_f_jr_0052; Film: 16mm
    - Formosa Land Reform, lewis_f_jr_0055; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - France, lewis_f_jr_0436; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - France (1), lewis_f_jr_0056; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - France (2), lewis_f_jr_0057; Film: 16mm
    - France (3), lewis_f_jr_0058; Film: 16mm
    - France (4), lewis_f_jr_0059; Film: 16mm
    - France (5), lewis_f_jr_0060; Film: 16mm
    - France (6), lewis_f_jr_0061; Film: 16mm
    - France (7), lewis_f_jr_0062; Film: 16mm
    - France (8), 07/26/1959; lewis_f_jr_0063; Film: 16mm
    - France (9), 04/19/1955; lewis_f_jr_0064; Film: 16mm
    - Franco, lewis_f_jr_0462; Film: 16mm, b/w, monaural
    - Franco (1), 04/11/1955; lewis_f_jr_0074; Film: 16mm
    - Franco (1), lewis_f_jr_0065; Film: 16mm
    - Franco (2), lewis_f_jr_0066; Film: 16mm
    - Franco (3), lewis_f_jr_0067; Film: 16mm
    - Franco (4), lewis_f_jr_0068; Film: 16mm
    - Franco (5), lewis_f_jr_0069; Film: 16mm
    - Franco (6), 02/14/1955; lewis_f_jr_0070; Film: 16mm
    - Franco (7), 04/02/1955; lewis_f_jr_0071; Film: 16mm
    - Franco (8), lewis_f_jr_0072; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Franco, lewis_f_jr_0514; Note on the leader reads: “Fulton Lewis Jr. No. 11”.; Film: 16mm
    - [Fulton Lewis, Jr. 6], 1953; lewis_f_jr_0499; Note on the leader in red crayon reads: “No. 4 I. P. K.”; Film: 16mm
    - [Fulton Lewis, Jr. 16], lewis_f_jr_0508; Film: 16mm
    - Fulton Lewis Jr "Show And" Pt 4, lewis_f_jr_0228; produced by William B. Dolph Radio Productions Barr Building; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Fulton Lewis Jr Alaska, lewis_f_jr_0229; produced by William B. Dolph Radio Productions Barr Building; Film: 16mm, b/w
    - Fulton Lewis Jr Pilot Film, lewis_f_jr_0227; produced by William B. Dolph Radio Productions Barr Building; Film: 16mm, b/w